Guide to the Mick Moloney Irish-American Music and Popular Culture Collection, Part II: Field Recordings AIA.031.002
Tamiment Library / Wagner Archives
- Series II: Non-digitized Tapes, 1956-2001
  - II:B Public Recordings
    - Unmarked. [Needs significant preservation work before digitization.], undated (Box 20, Item aiamm578R)
    - Unmarked. [Needs significant preservation work before digitization.], undated (Box 20, Item aiamm579R)
    - Unmarked. [Needs significant preservation work before digitization.], undated (Box 20, Item aiamm580R)
    - Unmarked. [Needs significant preservation work before digitization.], undated (Box 20, Item aiamm581R)
    - Unmarked. [Needs significant preservation work before digitization.], undated (Box 20, Item aiamm582R)
    - Unmarked. [Needs significant preservation work before digitization.], undated (Box 20, Item aiamm583R)
    - Unmarked. [Needs significant preservation work before digitization.], undated (Box 20, Item aiamm584R)
    - Unmarked. [Needs significant preservation work before digitization.], undated (Box 20, Item aiamm585R)
    - Unmarked. [Needs significant preservation work before digitization.], undated (Box 20, Item aiamm586R)
    - Unmarked. [Needs significant preservation work before digitization.], undated (Box 21, Item aiamm587R)
    - Unmarked. [Needs significant preservation work before digitization.], undated (Box 21, Item aiamm588R)
    - Unmarked. [Needs significant preservation work before digitization.], undated (Box 21, Item aiamm589R)
    - Unmarked. [Needs significant preservation work before digitization.], undated (Box 21, Item aiamm590R)
    - Unmarked. [Needs some preservation work before digitization.], undated (Box 20, Item aiamm567R)
    - Unmarked. 8-track reel., undated (Box 20, Item aiamm570R)
    - Williams, John (accordion), Moloney, Mick (banjo), Unidentified (whistle, guitar) in one concert medley; private performance by Seamus Connolly (fiddle); unidentified American teaching a tune to Moloney by lilting. (Length: 00:10:00), undated (Box 26, Item aiamm1207C)
    - "Women in Irish Music: Music for Mick’s Lecture." [Needs some preservation work before digitization.], undated (Box 27, Item aiamm1200C)
    - "Women in Irish Music: Tape for Lecture." Compilation of commercial recording excerpts. (Length: 00:45:00), undated (Box 26, Item aiamm1199C)
  - II:C Unprocessed, undated
    - Unprocessed field recordings including cassettes, reels, film, CDs and DATs (around 100 tapes)., undated (Box 36)
    - Unprocessed field recordings including cassettes and CDs (around 100 tapes)., undated (Box 37)
    - Unprocessed cassettes and reels including field recordings and re-recorded compilations of 78s., undated (Box 38)